{
    "id": "2550df68152140aab0a742ab5db4917c",
    "title": "Reported Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He said that he ...................... a toothache.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has got",
                "had got",
                "have got"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Manu said that he .................... very busy then.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She told us ....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that hurry up",
                "to hurry up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked her ........................ him a cup of water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "give",
                "giving",
                "to give"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she ...................... going to college.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju said that Gautam ..................... to go the following day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will have",
                "would have",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Geetha says that her father ...................... an Engineer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ........................ the physical test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has passed",
                "passed",
                "had passed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She told me that I .................. her only friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "have been",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He told me that he .................... me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loves",
                "is loving",
                "loved"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "James asked Mary .........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where was she going",
                "where she was going",
                "where has she gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}